<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<doc>
  <createremarks>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        If you create an instance of the <i>target class</i> for the first time, the <a href="html/9f1a9dc9-d91b-49fa-8a5b-c2ab8250c060.htm">weaver</a> creates an <i>interwoven type</i> which is the target class interwoven with
        all aspects. Subsequent calls requesting instances of the same target class will return instances of the same interwoven type. If an aspect does not
        match a <a href="html/a6898c0f-8a16-4ba2-acb9-cbd7f1efafce.htm">join-point</a> of the target class, the aspect will not be interwoven to
        the target class. The weaver uses a defined <a href="html/a6898c0f-8a16-4ba2-acb9-cbd7f1efafce.htm">interweaving order</a> to interweave more than one aspect.
      </para>
      <para>
        To prevent ambigous matches having multiple construcors in the targettype class use the <see cref="Loom._T&lt;TYPE&gt;"/> to specify the right constructor.
      </para>
      <para>
        Both overloaded methods <see cref="O:Loom.Weaver.Create"/> and <see cref="O:Loom.Weaver.CreateInstance"/> aren't lock-free. If a thread is creating an interwoven object for the first time, all 
        concurrent calls to these methods are blocked until the object is created. If you want to avoid this behaviour, 
        use a <see cref="Loom.IClassFactory{T}">class factory</see> by calling <see cref="O:Loom.Weaver.GetClassFactory"/>.
        If the first object of a type was created, all subsequent calls for creating objects of the same type will not block anymore.
      </para>
      <para>
        These methods are only available if you use dynamic weaving with <a href="html/9f1a9dc9-d91b-49fa-8a5b-c2ab8250c060.htm">Rapier-LOOM.NET</a>.
      </para>
    </remarks>
    <exception cref="Loom.AspectWeaverException">The aspect weaver was unable to interweave the target class.</exception>
    <exception cref="Loom.AbstractClassException">The interwoven target class has is still abstract methods.</exception>
    <exception cref="MethodInvocationException">There is no constructor that matches the specified parameters.</exception>
    <seealso cref="Aspect"/>
    <seealso cref="AspectAttribute"/>
    <seealso cref="Loom._T&lt;TYPE&gt;"/>
    <seealso cref="O:Loom.Weaver.GetClassFactory"/>
    <seealso cref="Loom.IClassFactory{T}"/>
    <seealso cref="O:Loom.Weaver.CreateInstance"/>
    <seealso cref="O:Loom.Weaver.Create"/>
  </createremarks>
</doc>